[
    {
        "questionNo": "Q1.",
        "question": "A non-finite verb agrees with the subject and conveys mood, tense, number, and person.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q2.",
        "question": "In subject-verb Agreements, it is the verb that impacts the subject.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q3.",
        "question": "Which sentence is correct?",
        "options": [
            "They goes to school.",
            "She go to school.",
            "He goes to school.",
            "Neon goes to school",
            "Both C and D"
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q4.",
        "question": "Fill in the blanks:<br> Twenty percent of the work ……………….just site visits.",
        "options": [
            "Is",
            "are"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q5.",
        "question": "Is the sentence below grammatically correct? <br> Three-fourth of the interns are graduates.",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q6.",
        "question": "Which sentence is grammatically correct?<br>1. Half of her family live in New Zealand.<br>2. Half of her family lives in New Zealand.",
        "options": [
            "Both 1 and 2",
            "only 1",
            "only 2",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q7.",
        "question": "When sentences start with “there” or “here,” the subject will always be placed ………….. the verb, so care needs to be taken to identify it correctly.",
        "options": [
            "Before",
            "After"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q8.",
        "question": "When ‘majority’/’minority’ refer to an undetermined number greater or less than 50%, use a ……………………………… verb:",
        "options": [
            "Plural",
            "Singular"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q9.",
        "question": "Which sentence is grammatically correct?<br>I. An 82% majority stand against this venture.<br>II. An 82% majority stands against this venture.",
        "options": [
            "Both I and II",
            "only I",
            "only II",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q10.",
        "question": "Fill in the blanks: <br>A majority of Indians ………………….voted against the quota system in education.",
        "options": [
            "Have",
            "Has"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q11.",
        "question": "Which sentence has no errors?<br>I. 200 dollars is the price of this bag.<br>II. 200 dollars are the price of this bag.",
        "options": [
            "Only II",
            "Only I",
            "Both I and II",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q12.",
        "question": "Fill in the blanks:<br> 117 km ...………………………….not a small distance.",
        "options": [
            "Are",
            "Were",
            "Is",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q13.",
        "question": "Seven days in jail ……………. a long time for someone who committed no crime.",
        "options": [
            "Were",
            "Are",
            "Is",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q14.",
        "question": "Is the sentence below grammatically correct?<br> These days the rich are getting richer.",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q15.",
        "question": "Fill in the blanks:<br> The number of patients registered in the psychiatric ward  ……………………………… 73.",
        "options": [
            "Are",
            "Is"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q16.",
        "question": "Fill in the blanks:<br> A number of lawyers ………………………..present in the protest.",
        "options": [
            "Is",
            "Are",
            "Was",
            "Were",
            "Both B and D"
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q17.",
        "question": "To which form of the verb, do we add an ‘s’ or ‘es’ to make it singular?",
        "options": [
            "First form",
            "Base form",
            "Infinitive form",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q18.",
        "question": "Which sentence is grammatically correct?<br>I. Half of the apple is gone.<br>II. Half of the apples are gone.",
        "options": [
            "Only II",
            "Only I",
            "Both",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q19.",
        "question": "Which is the finite verb in the sentence below:<br> Jonathan likes to drink coffee.",
        "options": [
            "Likes",
            "Drink",
            "To drink",
            "Both a and c"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q20.",
        "question": "Money, time and distance are frequently expressed by a ……………………… verb.",
        "options": [
            "Singular",
            "Finite",
            "Plural",
            "Non-finite"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    }
]

